# **Ashish Ranjan**

RZF 40B, Street no. 4, Mahavir Enclave Part 1, New Delhi 110077

Phone: 9999293144 – ashishranjan6644@gmail.com

### Summary

Workforce Analyst offering 2+ years and Industry experience of more than 6+ years of diversified experience. Excellent communication and problem-solving skills. Dedicated to achieving Client satisfaction as well as meeting or surpassing company expectations. Able to focus on projects, develop strategies and meet or exceed deadlines.

### Education

**M**aster of Business Administration (MBA), 2023 From Amity University, Noida, India

**B**achelor of Computer Application, 2018

Annamalai University — Annamalainagar, Tamil Nadu, India

Senior Secondary: Science, 2014 CBSE

## **Experience**

# Associate, Workforce Management, Concentrix June 2019 to Till Date — Gurgaon, Haryana

- Perform continual analysis of current performance (noting recent historical trends) and conduct real-time re-forecasting to make necessary adjustments in staffing plans and coordinate with Operations teams to achieve service level goals / business objectives for a multi-site operation.
- Maintain constant communication with Operations teams to coordinate needed staffing adjustments based on current and forecasted results.
- Produces call volume forecasts on a daily, weekly, monthly and annual basis for multi-site operation.
- Generates and evaluates staffing schedules, and ensures data updates into scheduling system.
   Generates short and long-term staffing models and provides recommendations based on analysis.
- Compares results to forecast and identify opportunities for improvement.
- Other related duties as assigned.

## Senior Representative, Concentrix October 2018 to May 2019 — Gurgaon, Haryana

- Handle customer queries through chats.
- Prompt response on chats.
- · Handle internal system to manage order flow.
- Resolve problems on customer related to Bills and phones.
- · Maintain CPH of 6 chats in an hour.
- Cross-trained and provided back-up for other customer service representatives when needed.

- Manage quality communication, customer support and product representation for each client.
- Guaranteed positive customer experiences and resolved all customer complaints.

# Senior Process Associate, Stealth Mode Pvt. Ltd. (Formerly Known as 'WBPROMOTIONS PVT. LTD.')

### **July 2017 - August 2018**

- Handle customer queries through phone calls, chats and emails.
- Convert inquiry calls/chats to sales.
- · Prompt response on emails.
- Handle internal system to manage order flow.
- Resolve problems on customer orders with vendors.
- · Converting leads to Sales. website inquiries per day, converting into renewal customers.
- Cross-trained and provided back-up for other customer service representatives when needed.
- Managed quality communication, customer support and product representation for each client.
- Guaranteed positive customer experiences and resolved all customer complaints.

# Customer Care Executive, WB Promotion August 2016 to April 2017 — Gurgaon, Haryana

- Handle customer queries through phone calls, chats and emails.
- · Convert inquiry calls/chats to sales.
- Prompt response on emails.
- Handle internal system to manage order flow.
- Resolve problems on customer orders with vendors.
- Converting leads to Sales, website inquiries per day, converting into renewal customers.
- Cross-trained and provided back-up for other customer service representatives when needed.
- Managed quality communication, customer support and product representation for each client.
- Guaranteed positive customer experiences and resolved all customer complaints.

#### Personal Details

Father's Name: Mr. Mahendra Mishra Mother's Name: Mrs. Munni Devi Date of Birth: 1st January 1997

Gender: Male

Marital Status : Single Nationality : Indian

Languages Known: Hindi, English.

Permanent address: - At – Morauna, PO. – Durgadih,

Rohtas, Bihar 802212

#### **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the information provided by me is true to my knowledge. I shall be responsible for any kind of inconvenience in future.

### **Ashish Ranjan**